JACKSON ROSE

Summary

Junior UX/UI Designer with a background in economics and managing a local start-up business. Experience in research, persona creation, wireframing, and prototyping to improve user experience. A team player who focuses on simplifying the lives of clients through simple creative solutions.

UX/UI Projects

Expert: specialist responsive web app Aug 2021- May 2022 Careerfoundry UX Study Case

- Set goals and conducted a thorough competitive analysis.
 Organized interviews and audience research including persona development through persona journey maps and user flows to create a real audience for the Expert app.
- Created sitemap, wireframes, and prototypes drafted a usability test script, proctored usability tests, and analyzed results that would act as the foundation for the Expert app.
- Coded HTML, converted a group of assets into deliverables, and used design principles to refine the Expert app to make it ready for launch.

Work Experience

Optycs Analytics General Manager

Jan 2021 - Current

 Oversaw business goals, budget, and daily activities. Managed and implemented business projects to reach goals and increase productivity and profit margins.

Arizona Asthma & Allergy Institute Jan 2020 – Feb 2020 Team Leader Over Back Office Records

 Organized, scanned, and uploaded confidential patient HIPPA as well as set up appointments for doctors to work with patients.

Guthrie Mainstream Services LLC May 2018 – Aug 2018 Provider

 Recorded behavior of patients providing important information to the company regarding their well-being.

Details

Phoenix, AZ (open to relocating)

480-662-2490

jacksonerose94@gmail.com

LinkedIn Profile

jacksoneroseux.wixsite.com/my-site

Skills

- UX/UI Research
- UX/UI Design
- Wireframing
- Prototyping
- Personas
- Competitive Analysis
- Usability Testing

Tools

- Adobe XD
- Figma
- Photoshop
- Sketch
- Marvel
- Miro

Education

Careerfoundry Aug 2021 - Current

Arizona State University Dec 2020 (B.A. Economics)

Utah State University Jan 2016 – May 2017

Languages

English (native)

Spanish (casual)